export const questions = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "What are not the semantic tags in HTML?",
    category: "HTML",
    points: 10,
    answerA: "<section> and <nav>",
    answerB: "<div> and <span>",
    answerC: "<figure> and <details>",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "How can we comment?",
    category: "HTML",
    points: 5,
    answerA: "// Comment",
    answerB: "# Comment",
    answerC: "<!-- Comment -->",
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What are the old lists to designing a page?",
    category: "HTML",
    points: 10,
    answerA: "<dl>, <dt> and <dd>",
    answerB: "<div> and <li>",
    answerC: "<figcaption> and <figure>",
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What are the names of classic CSS Frameworks?",
    category: "CSS",
    points: 15,
    answerA: "Semantic UI and UKit and Bulma",
    answerB: "React Modules and Styled Components",
    answerC: "Material UI and Grommet",
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What are the media types allowed?",
    category: "CSS",
    points: 10,
    answerA: "mobile and watch",
    answerB: "screen and tv",
    answerC: "jpg and png",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What are mixins?",
    category: "SASS",
    points: 10,
    answerA: "Is smiliar to a function block",
    answerB: "Is smiliar to a class block",
    answerC: "Is smiliar to a variable",
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the use of isNaN function?",
    category: "JavaScript",
    points: 30,
    answerA: "Is used to check if it is a number",
    answerB: "Check if value is an undefined",
    answerC: "Check if value is an illegal number",
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is a hoisting?",
    category: "JavaScript",
    points: 30,
    answerA: "All variables moved on bottom",
    answerB: "All Variables and functions moved on top",
    answerC: "All Variables moved on top",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is syntax of immediately invoked function?",
    category: "JavaScript",
    points: 20,
    answerA: "function () => {}",
    answerB: "(() => {})();",
    answerC: "const fn = () => {}",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What are the components?",
    category: "React",
    points: 35,
    answerA: "Components are the building blocks of application.",
    answerB: "Not a part of application",
    answerC: "Function block",
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
];
